Nice to meet you, I'm Eddie.
I would just like to ask, what makes someone
pro-crime versus anti-crime?
I think when you're soft on criminals,
when you let criminals out of prison,
when you pardon people who have assaulted police officers,
you're pro-criminal.
Donald Trump pardoned almost 1,600 people
who were involved in January the 6th.
I think 600 of them had been charged
with assaulting a police officer or obstructing a police officer.
170 had pled guilty to assaulting a police officer.
70 had pled guilty to assault with a deadly weapon.
J.D. Vance said, we're not going
to pardon the violent criminals from January 6th.
Donald Trump pardoned all of them.
Are you OK with that?
I would say January 6th is a very special case.
I would say it's almost a climax point in history.
I would just phrase the question this way.
Right now in the LA protests, if they were to, just
for example, they were to rush the capital of LA,
I mean, they'd have to move over all the homeless people living
in tents on the steps of the capital.
But if they were managed to get into the capital
and they were just protesting peacefully,
let's say police officers were rushing them in.
They were letting them in and saying, hey, you guys
can go in, like we have many testimonies that say.
What about the violent ones, though?
OK, violent ones like what?
Like a man named David Dempsey, a judge,
a Reagan-appointed judge sentenced to 20 years in prison.
He stomped on police officers' heads.
The judge said his conduct was exceptionally egregious.
He attacked police officers with flag poles and pepper spray.
Donald Trump pardoned him.
There's a man named Daniel Rodriguez.
12 years in prison for taking a stun gun
and tasing a police officer in the neck
and giving him a heart attack.
The judge said he was a one-man army of hate.
Donald Trump pardoned him.
Does that not make Trump pro-criminal?
He's letting violent criminals out of prison.
I would say no, it doesn't make him pro-criminal.
You're OK with that?
I did not say that.
I said that one pardon against somebody.
It was 1,600 pardons.
600 of those were people charged with.
Yes, one example that you just gave me.
I can give you more.
Should I keep going?
Fine, fine.
And I'll say the exact same thing every single time.
Then your argument will fall apart
because it's not just one example if I keep going.
Go for it then.
OK, Shane Jenkins, got seven years in prison
for nine criminal offenses, attacking police
with a deadly weapon, destroying government property.
Trump pardoned him.
How do pardons that probably shouldn't have happened
turn into pro-crime?
So you've agreed that they shouldn't have been pardoned.
Sure, but that wasn't your claim, was January 6.
Your claim was Trump is pro-crime.
Yeah, because he pardons criminals.
OK, I would say that that's a fault.
Let's talk about non-generous people.
He's pardoned people like Paul Wolchak recently,
who took millions of dollars from his own employees,
was sentenced to tax crimes, had to pay back $4 million.
Trump pardoned him.
He bought himself a $2 million yacht.
Why is he pardoning criminals like that?
Well, I don't know.
I don't think you should pardon.
I don't think really presidential pardon
should be a thing at all.
But I don't think that that means something.
All right, pause.
You've been voted out by the majority.
Please return to your seat.
Thanks.
How's it going?
Hey, how's it going?
Mehdi.
What is it?
You're from Northern UK, I guess?
I'm from London, North London.
OK, fair enough.
What's your ethnic background, if you don't mind my asking?
My parents are from India.
OK, perfect.
Just getting premise here.
First of all, I want to say that.
The premise of Donald Trump being pro-crime.
No, no, no.
I want to concern myself with why
you care about what's happening in the US, first and foremost.
Secondly, I want to say this.
Should US, should people who live in the US not care about?
Let's not interrupt each other.
I have this thing, like people know I have this thing.
I have to stay calm, OK?
Here's the thing.
I am happy that he released J6.
In fact, so much so that I was prepared to protest
if he didn't.
So when you say, are you OK that he's pro-crime?
Sure, because you know what?
We're changing the definition of what crime is,
first and foremost.
You don't think stomping on police officers' heads
is a crime?
I don't think it is.
It's no longer a relevant conversation anymore.
Really?
No, it's not, because you know what?
OK, have you seen the US in the last four or five years?
Yes, I've lived there for a while.
BLM protests, have you seen?
OK, I myself have been involved in these protests.
I've seen egregious things, things
that you couldn't even imagine.
So we have no rules there?
Being done to conservatives, it's not about that.
It's about tribal warfare.
That's where we're at in the US.
I don't know where you're at in the UK.
You're from India, so I don't really.
I'm not from India.
Oh, sorry, your parents are from India, so.
I'm an American citizen.
You have your own states.
I'm an American, you know.
You're an American citizen?
Yes.
OK, fair enough.
I don't know how you got that, but fair enough.
Here's the thing.
Are you an American citizen?
Absolutely, but here's the thing.
I'm not sure how you got that, but OK.
Born here.
OK.
I'm here in my family lineage as settlers from the 1500s,
so I have some stake in the claim here, OK?
But you're a descendant of immigrants, settlers,
colonialists.
Yeah, colonialists.
You don't look very Native American to me.
I am Native American.
Whites are Native Americans.
What are you talking about?
You're not.
Whites are Native Americans.
Really?
What was happening before the 1500s?
I think you're getting confused with me.
I don't mind going on a tangent, but what
was happening before the 1500s?
Calm down.
I think you're getting confused.
What was happening before the 1500s?
There was indigenous people here
that came here from Asia.
Do you know what indigenous means?
Listen, before America.
Indigenous people can't come from somewhere else.
Why do you ask a question if you're going to interrupt?
I'm not sure if you know what the meaning of indigenous means.
I do know what it means.
It means they came here first, right?
They came here from Asia by way of land bridge.
Have an argument with Neil deGrasse Tyson or anybody else
about that.
I don't care.
Is he an American?
I genuinely don't care.
Yes, he is.
OK.
Just checking.
My point is, my point is, OK?
Nothing to do with crime.
So far, you've agreed with me that these people are criminals.
Because you're derailing, dude.
I'm like, I'm trying to stay on track.
I'm not sure he sat down and asked me where I'm from.
I think you derailed this conversation from the get-go.
I think you got offended by that, but I'm always curious.
Because I'm always curious.
We're going to talk about immigration.
Don't worry.
Later on, you can come back.
I hope so.
Right now, you're doing a very bad job
of making the case that he's not pro-crime and pro-criminal.
I just got a round of applause.
I could probably get another one, actually, if I asked for it.
So I don't think I'm doing it bad.
Is this how you get rounds of applause?
You sit in a room with 20 people who agree with you?
Wow, amazing.
Amazing.
That must make you feel good.
You know what?
20 people who agree with you applauded you.
I'm actually glad you're getting this emotionally outraged
right now.
This is great.
I love it.
Do I have to say anything at this point,
or are you just going to keep going?
No, please.
Make your claim.
My claim is that I don't care if it's pro-crime.
You want to go back to the topic of conversation.
That's fine.
We agree, then.
He's pro-crime, and we don't care.
But I have a question for you, though.
Do you care on the opposite side of the spectrum?
Yes.
Do you care about law being administered
to the opposite side of the spectrum?
I think anyone who assaults a police officer
shouldn't be pardoned.
I think that Donald Trump shouldn't have pardoned
nine Republican members of Congress
who were convicted of crimes.
And I don't think Joe Biden should commit.
I don't think Democrats should pardon Democrats.
Fair.
But I don't think you understand where we are in the US, then.
I think I do.
No, because you're arguing for a position of a US that
doesn't exist anymore.
We're headed towards crime.
So nihilism, no laws, nothing matters.
Everyone's pro-crime.
It's not about that.
It's that conservatives for too long have been playing it safe.
They've been playing by the law.
They've been playing it by the book.
Yes, they have.
Maybe you missed the Bush presidency.
Did you live here during the Bush years?
Conservatives are so concerned.
They've been played by the law, George W. Bush, nor did
Ronald Reagan.
Let's be respectful to each other.
Let me finish.
I'm not sure you've been that respectful, but OK.
I'm trying to bring it back.
So let's both bring it back, OK?
I'm conservative, OK?
Really?
Let me tell you this.
We do play it too safe.
We've been playing it by the book for too long.
At this point, gloves are off, right?
The left has made their point.
They're willing to do it.
The police force in Washington, the left.